APOORVA MAJUMDAR

Experienced Business Development Specialist with 5 years of experience in Ecommerce industry, looking to seek a challenging position in an organization wherein the professional skills are used to benefit the organization as well as self-growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Specialist

ExclusiveLane | June 2021 - Present

- Handling Amazon account to increase sales through coupons, deals, discounting & working with the respective managers for the visibility on the platform.
- Managing advertising along with the agency by coordinating Amazon campaigns efficiently to achieve the set media plan monthly.
- Review analytics through reports in order to identify areas of success and areas of needing improvement.
- Working with excel to track all revenue potential, revenue delivered and other forecasting activities.
- Managed a team of 2 establishing tasks and deadlines.
- Identified problems successfully resolving the challenges faced.
- Collaborated across departments generating new strategies that upper management implemented.
- Also handled Amazon Vendor Central, Flipkart, Myntra, Tatacliq, Nykaa, Pepperfry, Ajio, Etsy & Urban Ladder Account.

E-Commerce Executive

Lasaki Step Up Pvt Ltd | June 2020 - May 2021

- Listing products via single and bulk upload on Amazon, Flipkart, Myntra, Etsy, Meesho & Shopclues.
- Running Sponsored Ads and Promotions.
- Analyzing traffic and researching relevant keywords.
- A+ Content (EBC) creation.
- Troubleshooting any issues on panels.
- Inventory and Price management.
- Managing FBA shipment.
- Making strategies to increase sales.

E-Commerce Executive

Paper Plane Design | May 2018 - March 2020

- Listing products via single and bulk upload on Amazon, Flipkart & Myntra.
- Running Sponsored Ads and Promotions.
- Analyzing traffic and researching relevant keywords.
- Troubleshooting any issues on panels.
- Inventory and Price management.
- Managing Vendor Central (Cloudtail & Appario).

EDUCATION:

Qualification	Year	University/School	Percentage
B.Sc.(Hon.) Mathematics	2014-2017	PGDAV College, University of Delhi	65%
XII (Science)	2012-2014	GBSSS Sarojini Nagar, New Delhi	72%
Х	2012	GBSS Kalkaji DDA Flats, New Delhi	78%

Contact:

Mobile No.: 8800755292

Email ID: majumdar921996@gmail.com

Address: 1328, Gali No. 8, Govindpuri, Kalkaji, New Delhi - 110019